<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animalia</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login" translatable="false">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password" translatable="false">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in" translatable="false">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short" translatable="false">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome" translatable="false">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username" translatable="false">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password" translatable="false">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed" translatable="false">"Login failed"</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label" translatable="false">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label" translatable="false">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next" translatable="false">Next</string>
    <string name="previous" translatable="false">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment" translatable="false">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment" translatable="false">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sign_in" translatable="false">SignInActivity</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="test2">test 2</string>
    <string name="Dog">Dog</string>
    <string name="Dog_text">The dog or domestic dog (Canis familiaris or Canis lupus familiaris) is a domesticated descendant of the wolf which is characterized by an upturning tail.    The dog derived from an ancient, extinct wolf,         and the modern grey wolf is the dog\'s nearest living relative.   The dog was the first species to be domesticated, by hunter–gatherers over 15,000 years ago, before the development of agriculture.         Due to their long association with humans, dogs have expanded to a large number of domestic individuals and gained the ability to thrive on a starch-rich diet that would be inadequate for other canids.            Over the millennia, dogs became uniquely adapted to human behavior, and the human-canine bond has been a topic of frequent study.         The dog has been selectively bred over millennia for various behaviors, sensory capabilities, and physical attributes.           Dog breeds vary widely in shape, size, and color. They perform many roles for humans, such as hunting, herding, pulling loads, protection, assisting police and the military, companionship, therapy, and aiding disabled people.            This influence on human society has given them the sobriquet of man\'s best friend.</string>
    <string name="share_additional">Share with us additional information!</string>
    <string name="write_comment">Comment...</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="Gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="Information">Information</string>
    <string name="Login">Login</string>
    <string name="Sign_Up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="Email">Email</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="Full_Name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="Login_btn">Login</string>
    <string name="Sign_Up_btn">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="Create_new_Account">Create new Account</string>
    <string name="Wrong_email_address">Wrong email address</string>
    <string name="Enter_Proper_Password">Enter Proper Password (at least 6 characters)</string>
    <string name="Please_Wait_While_Login...">Please Wait While Login...</string>
    <string name="Login_Successful">Login Successful</string>
    <string name="You_forgot_to_write_your_name">You forgot to write your name</string>
    <string name="Please_Wait_While_Registration...">Please Wait While Registration...</string>
    <string name="Registration">Registration</string>
    <string name="Registration_Successful">Registration Successful</string>
    <string name="Comment_is_empty...">Comment is empty...</string>
    <string name="Comment_Added">Comment Added</string>
    <string name="Lion">Lion</string>
    <string name="Lion_text">The lion (Panthera leo) is a large cat of the genus Panthera native to Africa and India. It has a muscular, deep-chested body, short, rounded head, round ears, and a hairy tuft at the end of its tail.\n\n It is sexually dimorphic, adult male lions are larger than females and have a prominent mane. It is a social species, forming groups called prides. A lion\'s pride consists of a few adult males, related females, and cubs. Groups of female lions usually hunt together, preying mostly on large ungulates. The lion is an apex and keystone predator, although some lions scavenge when opportunities occur and have been known to hunt humans, the species typically does not.\n\n The tail of all lions ends in a dark, hairy tuft that in some lions conceals an approximately 5 mm (0.20 in)-long, hard \"spine\" or \"spur\" that is formed from the final, fused sections of tail bone. The functions of the spur are unknown. The tuft is absent at birth and develops at around 5+1⁄2 months of age. It is readily identifiable by the age of seven months.\n\n Skeletal muscles of the lion make up 58.8% of its body weight and represents the highest percentage of muscles among mammals.</string>
    <string name="Horse">Horse</string>
    <string name="Horse_text">The horse (Equus ferus caballus) is a domesticated one-toed hoofed mammal. It belongs to the taxonomic family Equidae and is one of two extant subspecies of Equus ferus.\n\n Horses are adapted to run, allowing them to quickly escape predators, possessing an excellent sense of balance and a strong fight-or-flight response. Related to this need to flee from predators in the wild is an unusual trait: horses are able to sleep both standing up and lying down, with younger horses tending to sleep significantly more than adults.\n\n Female horses, called mares, carry their young for approximately 11 months, and a young horse, called a foal, can stand and run shortly following birth. Most domesticated horses begin training under a saddle or in a harness between the ages of two and four. They reach full adult development by age five, and have an average lifespan of between 25 and 30 years.\n\n Horse breeds are loosely divided into three categories based on general temperament: spirited \"hot bloods\" with speed and endurance; \"cold bloods\", such as draft horses and some ponies, suitable for slow, heavy work; and \"warmbloods\", developed from crosses between hot bloods and cold bloods, often focusing on creating breeds for specific riding purposes, particularly in Europe. There are more than 300 breeds of horse in the world today, developed for many different uses.</string>
    <string name="Giraffe">Giraffe</string>
    <string name="Giraffe_text">The giraffe is a tall African mammal belonging to the genus Giraffa. Specifically, It is an even-toed ungulate. It is the tallest living terrestrial animal and the largest ruminant on Earth. Traditionally, giraffes were thought to be one species, Giraffa camelopardalis, with nine subspecies. Most recently, researchers proposed dividing giraffes into up to eight extant species due to new research into their mitochondrial and nuclear DNA, as well as morphological measurements. Seven other extinct species of Giraffa are known from the fossil record.\n\n The giraffe\'s chief distinguishing characteristics are its extremely long neck and legs, its horn-like ossicones, and its spotted coat patterns. It is classified under the family Giraffidae, along with its closest extant relative, the okapi. Its scattered range extends from Chad in the north to South Africa in the south, and from Niger in the west to Somalia in the east. Giraffes usually inhabit savannahs and woodlands. Their food source is leaves, fruits, and flowers of woody plants, primarily acacia species, which they browse at heights most other herbivores cannot reach.\n\n Fully grown giraffes stand 4.3–5.7 m (14.1–18.7 ft) tall, with males taller than females. The average weight is 1,192 kg (2,628 lb) for an adult male and 828 kg (1,825 lb) for an adult female. Despite its long neck and legs, the giraffe\'s body is relatively short.  The skin of a giraffe is mostly gray, or tan, and can reach a thickness of 20 mm (0.79 in The 80–100 centimetres (31–39 in) long tail ends in a long, dark tuft of hair and is used as a defense against insects.</string>
    <string name="Crocodile">Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Crocodile_text">Crocodiles (family Crocodylidae) or true crocodiles are large semiaquatic reptiles that live throughout the tropics in Africa, Asia, the Americas and Australia.\n\n  A crocodile\'s physical traits allow it to be a successful predator. Its external morphology is a sign of its aquatic and predatory lifestyle. Its streamlined body enables it to swim swiftly, it also tucks its feet to the side while swimming, making it faster by decreasing water resistance. Crocodiles have webbed feet which, though not used to propel them through the water, allow them to make fast turns and sudden moves in the water or initiate swimming.\n\n   Webbed feet are an advantage in shallow water, where the animals sometimes move around by walking. Crocodiles have a palatal flap, a rigid tissue at the back of the mouth that blocks the entry of water. The palate has a special path from the nostril to the glottis that bypasses the mouth. The nostrils are closed during submergence.\n\n  Size greatly varies among species, from the dwarf crocodile to the saltwater crocodile. Species of the dwarf crocodile Osteolaemus grow to an adult size of just 1.5 to 1.9 m (4.9 to 6.2 ft), whereas the saltwater crocodile can grow to sizes over 7 m (23 ft) and weigh over 1,000 kg (2,200 lb). Several other large species can reach over 5.2 m (17 ft) long and weigh over 900 kg (2,000 lb).\n\n  Crocodilians show pronounced sexual dimorphism, with males growing much larger and more rapidly than females. Despite their large adult sizes, crocodiles start their lives at around 20 cm (7.9 in) long. The largest species of crocodile is the saltwater crocodile, found in eastern India, northern Australia, throughout South-east Asia, and in the surrounding waters.</string>
    <string name="Deer">Deer</string>
    <string name="Deer_text">Deer or true deer are hoofed ruminant mammals forming the family Cervidae.\n\n  Deer constitute the second most diverse family of artiodactyla after bovids. Though of a similar build, deer are strongly distinguished from antelopes by their antlers, which are temporary and regularly regrown unlike the permanent horns of bovids.\n\n  Characteristics typical of deer include long, powerful legs, a diminutive tail and long ears. Deer exhibit a broad variation in physical proportions. The largest extant deer is the moose, which is nearly 2.6 metres (8 ft 6 in) tall and weighs up to 800 kilograms (1,800 lb). The elk stands 1.4–2 metres (4 ft 7 in–6 ft 7 in) at the shoulder and weighs 240–450 kilograms (530–990 lb).\n\n  The northern pudu is the smallest deer in the world, it reaches merely 32–35 centimetres (12+1⁄2–14 in) at the shoulder and weighs 3.3–6 kilograms (7+1⁄4–13+1⁄4 lb). The southern pudu is only slightly taller and heavier. Sexual dimorphism is quite pronounced – in most species males tend to be larger than females, and, except for the reindeer, only males possess antlers.\n\n  Coat colour generally varies between red and brown, though it can be as dark as chocolate brown in the tufted deer or have a grayish tinge as in elk. Different species of brocket deer vary from gray to reddish brown in coat colour. Several species such as the chital, the fallow deer and the sika deer feature white spots on a brown coat. Coat of reindeer shows notable geographical variation.\n\n Deer are also excellent jumpers and swimmers. Deer are ruminants, or cud-chewers, and have a four-chambered stomach. Some deer, such as those on the island of Rùm, do consume meat when it is available.</string>
    <string name="Tiger">Tiger</string>
    <string name="Tiger_text">The tiger (Panthera tigris) is the largest living cat species and a member of the genus Panthera.\n\n It is most recognizable for its dark vertical stripes on orange fur with a white underside. An apex predator, it primarily preys on ungulates such as deer and wild boar. It is territorial and generally a solitary but social predator, requiring large contiguous areas of habitat, which support its requirements for prey and rearing of its offspring. Tiger cubs stay with their mother for about two years, then become independent and leave their mother\'s home range to establish their own.\n\n The tiger has a muscular body with powerful forelimbs, a large head and a tail that is about half the length of its body. Its pelage is dense and heavy, and colouration varies between shades of orange and brown with white ventral areas and distinctive vertical black stripes; the patterns of which are unique in each individual.\n\n There is notable sexual dimorphism between male and female tigers, with the latter being consistently smaller. The size difference between them is proportionally greater in the large tiger subspecies, with males weighing up to 1.7 times more than females. Males also have wider forepaw pads, enabling sex to be identified from tracks. It has been hypothesised that body size of different tiger populations may be correlated with climate and be explained by thermoregulation and Bergmann\'s rule, or by distribution and size of available prey species. \n\n Generally, males vary in total length from 250 to 390 cm (98 to 154 in) and weigh between 90 and 300 kg (200 and 660 lb) with skull length ranging from 316 to 383 mm (12.4 to 15.1 in). Females vary in total length from 200 to 275 cm (79 to 108 in), weigh 65 to 167 kg (143 to 368 lb) with skull length ranging from 268 to 318 mm (10.6 to 12.5 in). \n\n In either sex, the tail represents about 0.6 to 1.1 m (2 ft 0 in to 3 ft 7 in) of the total length. The Bengal and Siberian tigers are amongst the tallest cats in shoulder height. They are also ranked among the biggest cats that have ever existed reaching weights of more than 300 kg (660 lb). The tigers of the Sunda islands are smaller and less heavy than tigers in mainland Asia, rarely exceeding 142 kg (313 lb) in weight.</string>
    <string name="Dolphin">Dolphin</string>
    <string name="Dolphin_text">Dolphin is the common name of aquatic mammals within the infraorder Cetacea. \n\n Dolphins range in size from the relatively small 1.7-metre-long (5 ft 7 in) long and 50-kilogram (110-pound) bodied Maui\'s dolphin to the 9.5 m (31 ft 2 in) and 10-tonne (11-short-ton) killer whale. Dolphins can sometimes leap about 30 feet (9.1 m). Several species of dolphins exhibit sexual dimorphism, in that the males are larger than females. \n\n They have streamlined bodies and two limbs that are modified into flippers. Though not quite as flexible as seals, some dolphins can travel at speeds 29 kilometers (18 mi) per hour for short distances. \n\n Dolphins use their conical shaped teeth to capture fast-moving prey. They have well-developed hearing which is adapted for both air and water and is so well developed that some can survive even if they are blind. Some species are well adapted for diving to great depths. They have a layer of fat, or blubber, under the skin to keep warm in the cold water. \n\n The dolphin ear has specific adaptations to the marine environment. In humans, the middle ear works as an impedance equalizer between the outside air\'s low impedance and the cochlear fluid\'s high impedance. In dolphins, and other marine mammals, there is no great difference between the outer and inner environments. Instead of sound passing through the outer ear to the middle ear, dolphins receive sound through the throat, from which it passes through a low-impedance fat-filled cavity to the inner ear. The dolphin ear is acoustically isolated from the skull by air-filled sinus pockets, which allow for greater directional hearing underwater. \n\n  Dolphins are often regarded as some of Earth\'s most intelligent animals. Comparing species\' relative intelligence is complicated by differences in sensory apparatuses, response modes, and natures of cognition. The difficulty and expense of experimental work with large aquatic animals has so far prevented some tests and limited sample sizes and rigor in others. Compared to that of many other species, dolphin behavior has been studied extensively, in captivity and in the wild. See cetacean intelligence for more details.</string>
    <string name="Rhino">Rhino</string>
    <string name="Rhino_text">A rhinoceros, commonly abbreviated to rhino, is a member of any of the five extant species (or numerous extinct species) of odd-toed ungulates in the family Rhinocerotidae. \n\n Rhinoceroses are some of the largest remaining megafauna: all weigh at least one tonne in adulthood. They have a herbivorous diet, small brains (400–600 g) for mammals of their size, one or two horns, and a thick (1.5–5 cm), protective skin formed from layers of collagen positioned in a lattice structure. \n\n They generally eat leafy material, although their ability to ferment food in their hindgut allows them to subsist on more fibrous plant matter when necessary. Unlike other perissodactyls, the two African species of rhinoceros lack teeth at the front of their mouths; they rely instead on their lips to pluck food. \n\n Rhinoceros are killed by poachers for their horns, which are bought and sold on the black market for high prices, leading to most living rhinoceros species being considered endangered. The contemporary market for rhino horn is overwhelmingly driven by China and Vietnam, where it is bought by wealthy consumers to use in traditional Chinese medicine, among other uses. \n\n Rhino horns are made of keratin, the same material as hair and fingernails, and there is no good evidence of any health benefits. \n\n Adult rhinoceros have no real predators in the wild, other than humans. Young rhinos can however fall prey to big cats, crocodiles, African wild dogs, and hyenas.</string>
    <string name="Chameleon">Chameleon</string>
    <string name="Chameleon_text">Chameleons or chamaeleons (family Chamaeleonidae) are a distinctive and highly specialized clade of Old World lizards with 202 species described as of June 2015. These species come in a range of colours, and many species have the ability to change colour. \n\n Chameleons are distinguished by their zygodactylous feet, their swaying gait, and crests or horns on their brow and snout. Most species, the larger ones in particular, also have a prehensile tail. Chameleons\' eyes are independently mobile, but in aiming at a prey item, they focus forward in coordination, affording the animal stereoscopic vision. \n\n Chameleons are adapted for climbing and visual hunting. \n\n Some chameleon species are able to change their skin coloration. Different chameleon species are able to vary their coloration and pattern through combinations of pink, blue, red, orange, green, black, brown, light blue, yellow, turquoise, and purple. \n\n Chameleon skin has a superficial layer which contains pigments, and under the layer are cells with very small (nanoscale) guanine crystals. Chameleons change colour by \"actively tuning the photonic response of a lattice of small guanine nanocrystals in the s-iridophores\". This tuning, by an unknown molecular mechanism, changes the wavelength of light reflected off the crystals which changes the colour of the skin. The colour change was duplicated ex vivo by modifying the osmolarity of pieces of white skin. \n\n Colour change in chameleons has functions in camouflage, but most commonly in social signaling and in reactions to temperature and other conditions. \n\n All chameleons are primarily insectivores that feed by ballistically projecting their long tongues from their mouths to capture prey located some distance away. While the chameleons\' tongues are typically thought to be one and a half to two times the length of their bodies (their length excluding the tail), smaller chameleons (both smaller species and smaller individuals of the same species) have recently been found to have proportionately larger tongue apparatuses than their larger counterparts.</string>
    <string name="Monkey">Monkey</string>
    <string name="Monkey_text">Monkey is a common name that may refer to most mammals of the infraorder Simiiformes, also known as the simians. \n\n Many monkey species are tree-dwelling (arboreal), although there are species that live primarily on the ground, such as baboons. Most species are mainly active during the day (diurnal). Monkeys are generally considered to be intelligent, especially the Old World monkeys. \n\n Monkeys range in size from the pygmy marmoset, which can be as small as 117 millimetres (4.6 in) with a 172-millimetre (6.8 in) tail and just over 100 grams (3.5 oz) in weight, to the male mandrill, almost 1 metre (3.3 ft) long and weighing up to 36 kilograms (79 lb). Some are arboreal (living in trees) while others live on the savanna; diets differ among the various species but may contain any of the following: fruit, leaves, seeds, nuts, flowers, eggs and small animals (including insects and spiders). \n\n The many species of monkey have varied relationships with humans. Some are kept as pets, others used as model organisms in laboratories or in space missions. They may be killed in monkey drives (when they threaten agriculture) or used as service animals for the disabled. \n\n Some organizations train capuchin monkeys as service animals to assist quadriplegics and other people with severe spinal cord injuries or mobility impairments. After being socialized in a human home as infants, the monkeys undergo extensive training before being placed with disabled people. Around the house, the monkeys assist with daily tasks such as feeding, fetching, manipulating objects, and personal care. \n\n Some characteristics are shared among the groups,  most New World monkeys have prehensile tails while Old World monkeys have non-prehensile tails or no visible tail at all. Old World monkeys have trichromatic color vision like that of humans, while New World monkeys may be trichromatic, dichromatic, or—as in the owl monkeys and greater galagos—monochromatic. Although both the New and Old World monkeys, like the apes, have forward-facing eyes, the faces of Old World and New World monkeys look very different, though again, each group shares some features such as the types of noses, cheeks and rumps.</string>
    <string name="Koala">Koala</string>
    <string name="Koala_text">The koala or, inaccurately, koala bear (Phascolarctos cinereus), is an arboreal herbivorous marsupial native to Australia. \n\n It is easily recognisable by its stout, tailless body and large head with round, fluffy ears and large, spoon-shaped nose. The koala has a body length of 60–85 cm (24–33 in) and weighs 4–15 kg (9–33 lb). Fur colour ranges from silver grey to chocolate brown. Koalas from the northern populations are typically smaller and lighter in colour than their counterparts further south. These populations possibly are separate subspecies, but this is disputed. \n\n Koalas typically inhabit open eucalypt woodlands, and the leaves of these trees make up most of their diet. Because this eucalypt diet has limited nutritional and caloric content, koalas are largely sedentary and sleep up to 20 hours a day. \n\n  They are asocial animals, and bonding exists only between mothers and dependent offspring. Adult males communicate with loud bellows that intimidate rivals and attract mates. Males mark their presence with secretions from scent glands located on their chests. \n\n The pelage of the koala is thicker and longer on the back, and shorter on the belly. The ears have thick fur on both the inside and outside. The back fur colour varies from light grey to chocolate brown. The belly fur is whitish; on the rump it is dappled whitish, and darker at the back. The koala has the most effective insulating back fur of any marsupial and is highly resilient to wind and rain, while the belly fur can reflect solar radiation. \n\n The koala\'s curved, sharp claws are well adapted for climbing trees. The large forepaws have two opposable digits (the first and second, which are opposable to the other three) that allow them to grasp small branches. On the hindpaws, the second and third digits are fused, a typical condition for members of the Diprotodontia, and the attached claws (which are still separate) are used for grooming.</string>
</resources>